I'm Peppa Pig. Oink.
-This is my little brother George.
-Oink, oink!
This is Mommy Pig. Oink!
-And this is Daddy Pig.
-Oink!
[laughing]
Peppa Pig.
Edmond Elephant's Birthday.
[car horn plays "Taps"]
[narrator] Mr. Zebra the Postman
is delivering a letter to Peppa's house.
Oh, look.
Someone's got a party invitation.
It must be for me.
It says, "To George Pig,
from Edmond Elephant.
Please come to my party."
Doesn't it say "George and Peppa"?
-No. Just George.
-Hmmph.
I didn't want to go
to a silly baby party anyway.
[telephone ringing]
Hello?
Oh, it's for you, Peppa.
It's Emily Elephant.
-Hello.
-Hello, Peppa.
[rock music playing]
Do you want to come to Edmond's party
as my friend?
Oh, yes, please.
My mommy wants us to help
with the little ones.
Help? Yes, I can help.
Danny and Suzy are helpers, too.
Oh, goody.
[children laughing]
[narrator] Everyone is here
for Edmond Elephant's party.
[giggling]
Oh! The helpers are here.
[in unison] Hello, Mrs. Elephant.
Let's get this party started.
Who wants to play Musical Statues?
[in unison] Yay!
This is what you do.
Dance when the music is playing...
[polka music playing]
...and when it stops,
freeze like a statue.
[music stops]
Ready, steady, go.
[music starts]
Just dance already.
[laughing]
[music stops]
This one is still blinking.
You're out.
[sobbing]
[music starts, then stops]
You're moving, George. You're out.
[sobbing, then squeals]
Richard and Edmond are out.
So, Zaza is the winner.
Hooray!
You've got a medal.
It's made of real plastic gold.
-[giggles]
-[sobbing]
-Mommy, Musical Statues is over.
-[sobbing continues]
Lovely.
Now it's time for Pass the Parcel.
[all] Yay!
When the music plays,
pass the parcel round.
When the music stops, take some paper off.
Ready, steady, go.
[music starts]x
George. Pass the parcel.
[music stops]
[narrator] Edmond has got a medal.
-[laughs]
[music starts, then stops]
Hurry up, Richard.
Just take the paper off.
[narrator] Richard has got a medal.
-[giggles]
[music starts, then stops]
[narrator] George has got a medal.
Oink, oink! [giggles]
[music starts, then both grunting]
Pass the parcel.
[narrator]
Oh, dear. George isn't passing the parcel.
[music stops]
-Oink, oink! [giggles]
-[wails]
No, George. That's Zaza's medal.
[wails]
[music starts]
[music stops]
[laughs]
It's a giant teddy.
[narrator] Edmond has won.
[wailing]
Mommy, Pass the Parcel is finished.
Lovely. Now it's time for food.
[in unison] Hooray!
[giggling]
[narrator]
Oh, the helpers have taken all the seats.
This is Edmond's party, remember?
The helpers can eat after the little ones.
[in unison] Oh, yes.
We're the helpers.
Juice, please.
-Juice, please.
-Jelly, please.
-Jelly. Jelly.
More, please.
Happy birthday, Edmond.
[in unison] Happy birthday, Edmond.
[narrator] It is the end of the party.
Thank you to the helpers.
You all worked really hard.
Yes. It's not easy
looking after little children.
[sighs] I need to lie down.
I need a holiday.
[Peppa]
The Biggest Muddy Puddle in the World.
[narrator]
It is bedtime for Peppa and George.
Oink. There's so much rain.
That means there will be puddles
to jump in tomorrow.
-Oh, goody.
-You can never have too much rain.
[thunder rumbles]
[rooster crows]
[narrator] It is morning.
Hooray!
Muddy puddles.
-[giggling]
-[quacks]
Oh, hello, Mrs. Duck.
What are you doing here?
-Oink.
-[all] Wow.
[narrator] The rain has made a flood.
Our house is a desert island.
Muddy puddles, here I come. Wee!
-Oh?
-[quacks]
Who put all this water here?
How will we get our food?
Daddy will have to swim to the shops.
-Uh...
-[bell rings]
[narrator]
Grandpa Pig has arrived on his boat.
Ahoy, there. Wonderful boating weather.
Um...
Yes.
We're sailing to the shops.
Do you need anything?
Yes, please. Can you get us
some tomatoes and spaghetti?
Tomatoes and spaghetti.
[announcer] Polly Parrot copies everything
that is said.
Polly can be our shopping list.
-Who's a clever parrot?
-[squawks]
Who's a clever parrot?
-Can we come, too, please?
-Oink!
Hop aboard.
Look. There's Suzy Sheep's house.
We're going to the shops.
Do you need anything?
Mommy, do we need anything
from the shops?
[mommy sheep]
Yes. We need food for dinner.
Chocolate, please.
[squawks] Chocolate.
-Hello, Danny.
-[barks]
Hello, Peppa.
I'm helping my granddad.
-We're rescuing people.
-Great weather for it.
-Do you need anything from the shops?
-Uh...
Maybe a newspaper.
And a comic.
Newspaper. Comic.
Grandpa, what's that stick thing
in the water?
Ah! Submarine. Actions stations.
[bell rings, then alarm sounds]
Ahoy, there, me hearties.
[narrator]
It's Grampy Rabbit in his submarine.
Lovely day to go sailing
with just the sea and the sky.
-The stories I could tell--
-Do you need any shopping?
-Oh, yes. Uh, cheese, please.
-Cheese.
[narrator] Grandpa Pig's boat has arrived
at the supermarket.
Hello. It's very quiet today.
-You're my first customers.
-Oink. Maybe it's because of the flood.
Silly, isn't it?
A little bit of rain,
and everyone stays at home.
What can I get you?
Polly has a list.
Who's a clever parrot?
[narrator]
Oh, dear. Polly has forgotten the list.
Luckily, I remember what everyone wants.
Cheese.
Thank you, Peppa. You're a good 'un.
Newspaper and comic.
-Thanks, Peppa.
It was lucky Peppa was going to the shops,
or we'd have nothing for dinner.
Here's your chocolates.
Now we can have our dinner, Mommy.
[narrator]
Peppa and George have arrived back home.
It is their bedtime.
It is morning.
Oh!
[narrator] The water has gone
but left a big muddy puddle.
Muddy puddles.
[giggling]
This is the biggest muddy puddle
in the world, ever.
[Peppa] Santa's Grotto.
[narrator] It is Christmas Eve.
Hands up who wants to go
and see Father Christmas.
-Me. Me. Me.
Are we going to the North Pole?
Not quite that far, Peppa.
But Father Christmas lives
at the North Pole.
Lucky for us, he's got a grotto
at the Christmas fair.
[narrator] Peppa and George have come
to visit Santa's Grotto.
-Hello, everyone.
-[in unison] Hello.
All aboard the Elf Train.
This way to Santa's Grotto.
[train horn toots]
Suzy, what are you asking
Father Christmas For?
I don't know. What are you asking for?
I would like a doll that walks and talks
and closes its eyes when it goes to sleep.
I'll ask for that, too.
How does Father Christmas remember
what toys everybody wants?
He makes a list.
His sleigh must be very fast
to go around the whole world in one night.
It's a super sleigh.
Father Christmas is really old.
He's hundreds of years old.
Even older than my Daddy.
-Santa's Grotto.
-[children] Ooh!
Ho-ho-ho! Hello, everyone.
[in unison] Hello, Father Christmas.
-Have you all been good?
-Yes.
-Have you all kept your bedrooms tidy?
Have you?
Ha-ha-ho! Of course.
Now, come and tell me
what you'd like for Christmas.
[barks] Can I have a football, please?
-A xylophone.
-Tiddly winks.
-A magic set, please.
-Racing car.
[imitates racing car engine]
Bouncy ball. Boing! Boing!
A train, please.
A toy train.
Not a toy train. A real train.
One I can drive, with real passengers.
Ho, ho! I'll see what I can do.
Is that everyone?
We haven't seen you yet.
I am sorry. What is your name?
Oink. I'm Peppa Pig. We've met before.
Ah, yes. Nice to see you again, Peppa.
What would you like for Christmas?
I would like a doll that walks and talks
and closes its eyes when it goes to sleep,
please.
Um...
-The same for me, please.
-Very good.
You do know where I live, don't you?
Oh, yes.
How old are you?
Ho, ho! I'm hundreds of years old.
I told you.
Goodbye, Father Christmas.
-Don't forget to leave me a mince pie--
-And a drink.
We know.
And a carrot for the reindeer.
Ho-ho-ho!
[narrator] Peppa and her family
are driving back from the Christmas Fair.
Daddy, why have we got our bags
in the car?
We're spending Christmas
at Granny and Grandpa's house.
But Father Christmas won't know
where we are.
Don't worry, Peppa.
Father Christmas knows everything.
[horn honks]
Granny Pig. It's nearly Christmas.
Yes, and I've got a very important job
for you.
Stir the Christmas pudding
and make a wish.
[narrator]
Peppa and George are making a wish.
Racing car.
Oh, don't tell me what it is.
Here's the mince pie and a drink
for Father Christmas.
And a carrot for the reindeer.
[doorbell chimes]
Who can that be at this time of night?
We're not buying anything.
♪ Merry, joyful greetings
Festive, happy cheer ♪
Carol singers.
♪ Snow is falling gently
Christmas time is here ♪
Oh, Merry Christmas.
[narrator]
It is bedtime for Peppa and George.
This used to be my bedroom
when I was a little piggy.
Father Christmas knows
where Granny and Grandpa live, doesn't he?
Oh, yes. He's been here many times before.
Good night, Peppa. Good night, George.
[snoring]
[narrator]
Peppa and George have fallen asleep.
When they wake up,
it will be Christmas day.
[Peppa] Santa's Visit.
[narrator]
It is very early on Christmas morning.
Peppa and her family are staying
at Granny and Grandpa Pig's house.
George, wake up.
-Oink, oink!
-Santa's been.
Bubble mix.
Comics.
And tangerines.
Mommy. Daddy. It's Christmas.
-Eh? What?
-It's too early, Peppa.
Go and say Happy Christmas
to Granny and Grandpa.
[snoring]
Granny. Grandpa.
[screams]
UDon't panic. All hands on deck. [snorts]
It's Christmas.
It's three o'clock in the morning.
But Santa's been.
Can we see if he's still here?
No, Santa's not here.
Look, the carrot, drink and mince pie
have gone.
He's only left crumbs.
Yes. Santa likes a good mince pie.
And there are big presents under the tree.
I asked Santa for a doll.
Can we open them now?
We will open the big presents
after Christmas lunch.
Oh, goody.
[narrator] Peppa and her family
are having Christmas lunch.
Let's pull the crackers.
There are paper hats inside.
And party trumpets.
And jokes.
-What wobbles in the sky?
-I don't know.
A jelly copter.
-Mmm. This Christmas pudding is delicious.
-Peppa and George helped me make it.
-We did the stirring.
-Did you make a wish, Peppa?
-Yes, I wished for--
-Don't tell us.
Let's open the presents.
Yippee!
This one is for George.
Oink, oink!
[narrator] It is a racing car set.
[Grandpa] This looks a bit complicated.
Let me see.
This goes here, and that goes there,
and this goes there.
Oink! Let's race.
Ready, steady, go.
[imitating car engine]
[narrator] Daddy and Grandpa
are enjoying playing racing cars.
-Isn't that George's present?
-[laughs]
I think George is quite happy
playing with the box.
[imitates car engine]
This is your present, Daddy Pig.
-Ah! Socks.
-And I've got socks.
-Socks.
-[all laughing]
So, the last present must be for--
Me. I asked Santa
for a doll that walks and talks
and closes its eyes when it goes to sleep.
Oh!
Birdseed?
Birdseed.
That present is for Polly Parrot.
But it was the last one.
Santa has forgotten me.
[ringing]
-Hello?
-[bleats]
Can I talk to Peppa, please?
Peppa. It's Suzy Sheep.
Hello, Suzy.
-Did you get your doll?
-No.
I got mine.
It cries and laughs
and closes its eyes and everything.
Santa's given you my doll.
No. The label says, "For Suzy Sheep."
Oink. Then Santa has forgotten me.
Ho-ho-ho!
[narrator] Santa is on his way home.
That's the last of this year's toys
delivered.
Oh! What's this at the bottom of my sack?
Santa can't have forgotten you.
I have been a good piggy, haven't I?
Ho-ho-ho!
Santa.
-Uh... Hello.
-He came down our chimney.
Of course he did, Granny.
Here's your present, Peppa.
Sorry it's a bit late.
[giggles] My doll.
Thank you, Santa.
-Would you like some Christmas pudding?
-George and I stirred it and made wishes.
Mmm! Yummy.
And I wished that Santa would visit us
on Christmas Day.
And you did.
Ho-ho-ho!